An adventure on a world beyond the stars.
Ewoks: The Battle for Endor is a adventure, family,
tv movie film directed by Jim Wheat.
The army of the Marauders, led by King Terak and the witch Charal,
attack the Ewoks village, killing Cindel's family.
Cindel and the Ewok Wicket escape and meet Teek in the
forest, a naughty and very fast animal.
Teek takes them to a house in which an old man, Noa, lives.
Like Cindel, he also crashed with his Starcruiser on Endor.
Together they fight Terak and Charal.
Noa Briqualon, played by Wilford Brimley.
Wicket W. Warrick, played by Warwick Davis.
Cindel Towani, played by Aubree Miller.
Charal, played by Siân Phillips.
Terak, played by Carel Struycken.
Teek, played by Niki Botelho.
Ewoks: The Battle for Endor is a 1985 American television film set in the Star Wars universe
and co-written and directed by Jim and Ken Wheat from a story by George Lucas.
A sequel to Caravan of Courage: An Ewok Adventure, it focuses on Cindel Towani, the human girl from the first film, who, after being
orphaned, joins the Ewoks in protecting their village and defeating the marauders who have taken control of the Endor moon.
The film premiered on ABC on November 24, 1985.
The film explores themes of kingdom, village, liberation, coronation, miracle.
The tone is thought_provoking.